So, you know, they just making up Antifa to make up a reason to lock people up.
Just like we did with cartels. We're going to take the same approach, President Trump, with Antifa. Destroy the entire organization from top to bottom.
We're going to take them apart. Thanks to your bold leadership and the designation of Antifa as a terrorist organization, which is exactly what they are.
Americans will no longer tolerate their unhinged violence.
I mean, it's like race. They they made up race to legitimize enslaving black people.
Right. The ruling class also created terrorism like they they they were doing terrorism and then they created and packaged it because, you know, they know how to market so that they could legitimize applying it to an entire group of people.
The Arabs, while accusing them of doing the thing that they were doing.
This is their flow. You know that that like because Antifa is not a real thing.
So they're making it a real thing. That was chocolate.
Greedy. But yeah, they're literally just making Antifa into a real thing so that they have a real reason to lock your real hour real butt up.
But. That's what that's what that's what they're doing, if you weren't sure.
And I want to be clear for everybody out here who wants to say it's not me.
This is an example of how they can just create legitimacy around criminality.
So you might not be caught up in the Antifa definition right now, but if you don't think they'll create a legitimacy to make you a criminal if it serves them, well, then, baby, you ain't paying enough attention.
You might not be caught up in the Antifa.